(Priya:)Does that sound like fun?
Yeah!
(Leonard:)Dodgers are baseball,
right?
(Priya:)You'll need to explain
the game to me.
(Leonard:)Mm, it's complicated.
(Leonard:)But as I remember it,
the essentials are
"get chosen last, get hit
by the ball, cry, go home."
(Priya:)Well, regardless,
I've got four tickets.
(Priya:)And I was thinking we can bring
Bernadette and Howard.
(Priya:)She's really interesting,
and I bet I can get used to him.
(Leonard:)Well, it might not
be a great idea
(Leonard:)to invite those two.
Why not?
(Leonard:)Don't tell anybody
I told you,
(Leonard:)but I heard she might
be breaking up with him.
(Priya:)Oh... too bad...
(Priya:)Although I do know one person
for whom that's good news.
(Leonard:)Really? Who?
(Priya:)My brother.
(Priya:)He's got a big crush
on Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)What?
(Priya:)You're kidding.
No. I found poems
he wrote about her.
(Priya:)Very disturbing.
"Oh, Bernadette,
please play my clarinet."
(Leonard:)Wow, that's hard to believe.
Yes.